Guide to the Judson Memorial Church Archive MSS.094
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Accretion 2009 - Series C: General Archives
  - Subseries 5: Committees
    - Oral History/Archives Group, 1998 (Box .09.11, Folder 7)
    - Ordination Committee, 1985 (Box .09.11, Folder 8)
    - Ordination Committee, 1986 (Box .09.11, Folder 9)
    - Ordination Committee, 1987 (Box .09.11, Folder 10)
    - Ordination Committee, 1988 (Box .09.11, Folder 11)
    - Ordination Committee, 1989 (Box .09.11, Folder 12)
    - Ordination Committee, 1990-1993 (Box .09.11, Folder 13)
    - Ordination Committee, 1995-1999 (Box .09.11, Folder 14)
    - Personnel Committee, 1981 (Box .09.11, Folder 15)
    - Personnel Committee, proposal to provide retirement housing for Howard Moody, 1985 (Box .09.11, Folder 16)
    - Personnel Committee, 1991 (Box .09.11, Folder 17)
    - Personnel Committee, 1992 (Box .09.11, Folder 18)
    - Personnel Committee - interim pastor job description, 1992 (Box .09.11, Folder 19)
    - Personnel Committee, 1993 (Box .09.11, Folder 20)
    - Personnel Committee, 1994 (Box .09.11, Folder 21)
    - Personnel Committee, 1995 (Box .09.11, Folder 22)
    - Personnel Committee, 1996 (Box .09.11, Folder 23)
    - Personnel Committee, 1997 (Box .09.11, Folder 24)
    - Personnel Committee, 1998 (Box .09.11, Folder 25)
    - Personnel Committee, 1999 (Box .09.11, Folder 26)
    - Search Committee, 1991-1993 - interim pastor, enquiry of interest letters (Box .09.11, Folder 27)
    - Search Committee, 1991-1993 - interim pastor interview packet, 1992 (Box .09.11, Folder 28)
    - Search Committee, 1991-1993 - interim pastor Malcomson, 1992 (Box .09.11, Folder 29)
    - Search Committee, 1991-1993 - senior minister, 1992-1993 (Box .09.11, Folder 30)
    - Search Committee, 1991-1993 - church profile (Box .09.11, Folder 31)
    - Search Committee, 1991-1993 - selection of Peter Laarman (Box .09.11, Folder 32)
    - Social Concerns Committee, 1980-1990 (Box .09.11, Folder 33)
    - Social Concerns Committee - survey of interests, 1981 (Box .09.11, Folder 34)
    - Social Concerns Committee - questionnaire, 1982 (Box .09.11, Folder 35)
    - Social Concerns Committee, 1989 (Box .09.11, Folder 36)
    - Social Concerns Committee, 1990 (Box .09.11, Folder 37)
    - Social Concerns Committee - march on Washington, 26 Jan 1991 (Box .09.11, Folder 38)
    - Social Concerns Committee, 1991-1992 (Box .09.11, Folder 39)
    - Social Concerns Committee, 1993 (Box .09.11, Folder 40)
    - Social Concerns Committee - questionnaire, 1994 (Box .09.11, Folder 41)
    - Social Concerns Committee, 1994 (Box .09.11, Folder 41)
    - Social Concerns Committee, 1995 (Box .09.11, Folder 43)
    - Social Concerns Committee, 1996 (Box .09.11, Folder 44)
    - Social Concerns Committee, 1997 (Box .09.11, Folder 45)
    - Staff - job descriptions, 1984-2000 (Box .09.11, Folder 46)
    - Staff - re: Congregation's access to salary info, legal opinion, 8 Jul 1993 (Box .09.11, Folder 47)
    - Staff, [1996] (Box .09.11, Folder 48)
    - Staff - personnel policies, 1996 (Box .09.11, Folder 49)
    - Staff - hiring of clergy staff, 1996-1999 (Box .09.11, Folder 50)
    - Structure & Governance Committee - evaluation of implementation, 1998 (Box .09.11, Folder 51)
    - Summer Worship Committee, 1980-1989 (Box .09.11, Folder 52)
    - Summer Worship Committee, 1990 (Box .09.11, Folder 53)
    - Summer Worship Committee, 1991 (Box .09.11, Folder 54)
    - Summer Worship Committee, 1993 (Box .09.11, Folder 55)
    - Summer Worship Committee, 1994 (Box .09.11, Folder 56)
    - Sunday School Committee, 1980s (Box .09.11, Folder 57)
    - Sunday School Committee - Attendance, 1986-1992 (Box .09.11, Folder 58)
    - Sunday School Committee, 1986 (Box .09.11, Folder 59)
    - Sunday School Committee, 1987 (Box .09.11, Folder 60)
    - Sunday School Committee, 1988 (Box .09.11, Folder 61)
    - Sunday School Committee - Picnic planning, 1988-1994 (Box .09.11, Folder 62)
    - Sunday School Committee, 1989 (Box .09.11, Folder 63)
    - Sunday School Committee, 1990-1991 (Box .09.11, Folder 64)
    - Sunday School Committee, 1991-1992 (Box .09.11, Folder 65)
    - Sunday School Committee, 1992-1993 (Box .09.12, Folder 1)
    - Sunday School Committee, 1993-1994 (Box .09.12, Folder 2)
    - Sunday School Committee, 1994-1995 (Box .09.12, Folder 3)
    - Sunday School Committee, 1995-1996 (Box .09.12, Folder 4)
    - Sunday School - Curriculum, Preschool, 1995-1996 (Box .09.12, Folder 5)
    - Sunday School - Curriculum, 1st-3rd grade, 1995-1996 (Box .09.12, Folder 6)
    - Sunday School - Curriculum, 4th-6th grade, 1995-1996 (Box .09.12, Folder 7)
    - Sunday School Committee, 1996-1997 (Box .09.12, Folder 8)
    - Sunday School Committee, 1997-1998 (Box .09.12, Folder 9)
    - Sunday School Committee, 1998-1999 (Box .09.12, Folder 10)
    - Sunday School Committee, 1999-2000 (Box .09.12, Folder 11)
    - Worship Committee (ad-hoc), 1980-1982 (Box .09.12, Folder 12)
    - Worship Committee, 1994 (Box .09.12, Folder 13)
  - Subseries 6: Worship Materials
    - Songbooks - Judson Kids Songbook, undated (Box .09.12, Folder 14)
    - Songbooks - "Go to Galilee and other songs" by Al Carmines, 1974 (Box .09.12, Folder 15)
    - Songbooks - list of songs, undated (Box .09.12, Folder 16)
    - Songbooks - Judson Weekend Songbook & supplement, 1988 (Box .09.12, Folder 17)
    - Songbooks - Contemporary Songs for Worship (Judson) in red binder with source list, undated (Box .09.12, Folder 18)
    - Songbooks - Judson Centennial Songbook, 1990 (Box .09.12, Folder 19)
    - Songbooks - Judson Christmas Songbook, undated (Box .09.12, Folder 20)
    - Songbooks - Songbook of Hymns (Judson), undated (Box .09.12, Folder 21)
    - Worship Materials - Service of Petition for the Moratorium (Vietnam War), 15 Oct 1969 (Box .09.12, Folder 22)
    - Worship Materials - Celebration of the City, 10 Nov 1991 (Box .09.12, Folder 23)
    - Worship Materials - Celebration of the City, 23 Oct 1994 (Box .09.12, Folder 24)
    - Worship Materials - Performance/Ritual, Body/Relief, 13 Oct 1996 (Box .09.12, Folder 25)
    - Worship Materials - World AIDS Day, 1 Dec 1996 (Box .09.12, Folder 26)
    - Worship Materials - A Judson Christmas Celebration, 15 Dec 1996 (Box .09.12, Folder 27)
    - Worship Materials - Maundy Thursday, 27 Mar 1997 (Box .09.12, Folder 28)
    - Worship Materials - on dance, 12 Oct 1997 (Box .09.12, Folder 29)
    - Worship Materials - on dance, 14 Dec 1997 (Box .09.12, Folder 30)
    - Worship - Summer & Fall Schedules, 1998 (Box .09.12, Folder 31)
    - Worship Materials - A Service of Remembering, 28 Feb 1999 (Box .09.12, Folder 32)
    - Worship Materials - Strength for the Struggle, A Lenten Reflection Series, 1999 (Box .09.12, Folder 33)
    - Worship - Summer Worship, 1999 (Box .09.12, Folder 34)
    - Worship - Bulletins, Jan-Jun 1995 (Box .09.12, Folder 35)
    - Worship - Bulletins, Jul-Dec 1995 (Box .09.12, Folder 36)
    - Worship - Bulletins, Jan-Jun 1996 (Box .09.12, Folder 37)
    - Worship - Bulletins, Jul-Dec 1996 (Box .09.12, Folder 38)
    - Worship - Bulletins, Jan-Jun 1997 (Box .09.12, Folder 39)
    - Worship - Bulletins, Jul-Dec 1997 (Box .09.12, Folder 40)
    - Worship - Bulletins, Jan-Jun 1998 (Box .09.12, Folder 41)
    - Worship - Bulletins, Jul-Dec 1998 (Box .09.12, Folder 42)
    - Worship - Bulletins, Jan-Jun 1999 (Box .09.12, Folder 43)
    - Worship - Bulletins, Jul-Dec 1999 (Box .09.12, Folder 44)
    - Worship - Bulletins, Jan-Jun 2000 (Box .09.12, Folder 45)
    - Worship - Bulletins, Jul-Dec 2000 (Box .09.12, Folder 46)
  - Subseries 7: Publications (in-house)
    - Mailings to Congregation, 1970-1984 (Box .09.13, Folder 1)
    - Mailings to Congregation - letter announcing K. Senecal's hiring, 2000 (Box .09.13, Folder 2)
    - Publications - Christmas Appeal, 1978-1979 (Box .09.13, Folder 3)
    - Publications - Christmas Appeal, 1980-1989 (Box .09.13, Folder 4)
    - Publications - Christmas Appeal, 1990, 1991, 1994-2000 (Box .09.13, Folder 5)
    - Publications - Restoration of the La Farge Windows, 1995 (Box .09.13, Folder 6)
    - Publications - Newsnotes, 1995 (Box .09.13, Folder 7)
    - Publications - Newsnotes, 1996 (Box .09.13, Folder 8)
    - Publications - Newsnotes, 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 9)
    - Publications - Newsnotes, 1998 (Box .09.13, Folder 10)
    - Publications - Newsnotes, 1999 (Box .09.13, Folder 11)
    - Publications - Newsnotes, 2000 (Box .09.13, Folder 12)
    - Publications - Judson Windows, 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 13)
    - Publications - Judson Windows, 1995 (Box .09.13, Folder 14)
    - Publications - Judson Windows, 1996 (Box .09.13, Folder 15)
    - Publications - Judson Windows, 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 16)
    - Publications - Judson Windows, 1998 (Box .09.13, Folder 17)
    - Publications - Judson Windows, 1999 (Box .09.13, Folder 18)
    - Publications - Judson Windows, 2000 (Box .09.13, Folder 19)
    - User's Guide to Judson Memorial Church, undated (Box .09.13, Folder 20)
    - Remembering the Judson House - correspondence, 2000 (Box .09.13, Folder 21)
  - Subseries 8: Minister-Generated materials
    - Carmines - "Christmas Rappings," vinyl test pressing documentation, 27 Nov 1979 (Box .09.13, Folder 22)
      Vinyl pressings available in Accretion 2009 - Series G: Subseries 5.
    - Green Sermons - "Is There Living Water Left?", 10 Mar 1996 (Box .09.13, Folder 23)
    - Green - liturgy, 8 Sep 1996 (Box .09.13, Folder 24)
    - Green Sermons - "Checking the Pulse", 15 Sep 1996 (Box .09.13, Folder 25)
    - Green - liturgy, 29 Sep 1996 (Box .09.13, Folder 26)
    - Green Sermons - "Who is Jesus Now?", 6 Oct 1996 (Box .09.13, Folder 27)
    - Green - liturgy, 20 Oct 1996 (Box .09.13, Folder 28)
    - Green Sermons - "Christian-Jewish Dialogue: A Personal Journey", 27 Oct 1996 (Box .09.13, Folder 29)
    - Green - liturgy, 3 Nov 1996 (Box .09.13, Folder 30)
    - Green Sermons - "Life After the Election", 10 Nov 1996 (Box .09.13, Folder 31)
    - Green Sermons - "Grace and Gratitude", 24 Nov 1996 (Box .09.13, Folder 32)
    - Green Sermons - "Yielding to Advent", 8 Dec 1996 (Box .09.13, Folder 33)
    - Green - liturgy, 29 Dec 1996 (Box .09.13, Folder 34)
    - Green - liturgy, 5 Jan 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 35)
    - Green Sermons - "Creativity & Chaos", 12 Jan 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 36)
    - Green - liturgy, 26 Jan 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 37)
    - Green Sermons - "Talking About Genesis: Happy Endings", 2 Feb 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 38)
    - Green - liturgy, 9 Feb 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 39)
    - Green - liturgy, 12 Feb 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 40)
    - Green Sermons - "Sin, Wilderness and the Rainbow" - First Presbyterian, El Paso, Texas, 16 Feb 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 41)
    - Green Sermons - "Immigrant Bias in America", 23 Feb 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 42)
    - Green Sermons - "What is Agape Anyway", 2 Mar 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 43)
    - Green - liturgy, 9 Mar 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 44)
    - Green Sermons - "On the Dangerous Path", 16 Mar 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 45)
    - Green Sermons - "Living the Resurrection", 30 Mar 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 46)
    - Green - liturgy, 6 April 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 47)
    - Green Sermons - "Healing, Wholeness & Doubt", 13 April 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 48)
    - Green Sermons - "Evangelism is a Dirty Word", 27 Apr 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 49)
    - Green Sermons - "May Day Musing", 4 May 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 50)
    - Green Sermons - "Holocaust Memorial Day", 4 May 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 51)
    - Green - liturgy, 11 May 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 52)
    - Green - liturgy, 18 May 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 53)
    - Green Sermons - "Whom Shall I Say is Calling?", 25 May 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 54)
    - Green - liturgy, 1 Jun 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 55)
    - Green Sermons - "Songs from Antigone", 8 Jun 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 56)
    - Green Sermons - "Father Knows Best", 15 Jun 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 57)
    - Green Sermons - "Post-Gay Syndrome", 29 Jun 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 58)
    - Green Sermons - "Words of Remembrance - for Gigi", 22 Jul 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 59)
    - Green - liturgy, 27 Jul 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 60)
    - Green Sermons - "Tales from the Apocrypha", 3 Aug 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 61)
    - Green Sermons - "Standing on the Promises", 10 Aug 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 62)
    - Green - liturgy, 17 Aug 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 63)
    - Green - liturgy, 7 Sep 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 64)
    - Green - liturgy, 14 Sep 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 65)
    - Green Sermons - Meditation, 21 Sep 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 66)
    - Green Sermons - "The Mysteries of John", 28 Sep 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 67)
    - Green - liturgy, 5 Oct 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 68)
    - Green Sermons - "Called to Freedom", 26 Oct 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 69)
    - Green Sermons - "Meeting Death", 2 Nov 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 70)
    - Green Sermons - "The Ultimate Punishment", 16 Nov 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 71)
    - Green Sermons - "Facing the Light", 30 Nov 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 72)
    - Green - liturgy, 7 Dec 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 73)
    - Green - liturgy, 21 Dec 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 74)
    - Green - liturgy, 28 Dec 1997 (Box .09.13, Folder 75)
    - Green - liturgy, 4 Jan 1998 (Box .09.13, Folder 76)
    - Green Sermons - "Parents & Grown-Up Kids", 11 Jan 1998 (Box .09.13, Folder 77)
    - Green - liturgy, 18 Jan 1998 (Box .09.13, Folder 78)
    - Green Sermons - "The Message & the Kingdom", 1 Feb 1998 (Box .09.13, Folder 79)
    - Green - liturgy, 8 Feb 1998 (Box .09.13, Folder 80)
    - Green Sermons - "The Language of Love", 15 Feb 1998 (Box .09.13, Folder 81)
    - Green - liturgy, 22 Feb 1998 (Box .09.13, Folder 82)
    - Green - liturgy, 25 Feb 1998 (Box .09.13, Folder 83)
    - Green Sermons - "Reading Ruth & Naomi", 8 Mar 1998 (Box .09.13, Folder 84)
    - Green - liturgy, 15 Mar 1998 (Box .09.13, Folder 85)
    - Green Sermons - "Sin City to New Creation", 22 Mar 1998 (Box .09.13, Folder 86)
    - Green - liturgy, 29 Mar 1998 (Box .09.13, Folder 87)
    - Green Sermons - "Recognizing the Time", 5 Apr 1998 (Box .09.13, Folder 88)
    - Green - liturgy, 9 Apr 1998 (Box .09.13, Folder 89)
    - Green Sermons (for First Presbyterian Church), 10 Apr 1998 (Box .09.13, Folder 90)
    - Green - liturgy, 12 Apr 1998 (Box .09.13, Folder 91)
    - Green Sermons - "Paul's Big Call: Igniting the Revolution", 26 Apr 1998 (Box .09.13, Folder 92)
    - Green - liturgy, 3 May 1998 (Box .09.13, Folder 93)
    - Green Sermons - "Mothers Everywhere", 10 May 1998 (Box .09.13, Folder 94)
    - Green Sermons - "What Matters Most", 7 Jun 1998 (Box .09.13, Folder 95)
    - Green Sermons - "Celebration of the Life of Miriam Corbett", 14 Jun 1998 (Box .09.13, Folder 96)
    - Green Sermons - "Summer Light", 21 Jun 1998 (Box .09.13, Folder 97)
    - Laarman Sermons - "A Bloodless Thanksgiving", 2 Oct 1993 (Box .09.13, Folder 98)
    - Laarman Sermons - "In Dreams Begin Responsibilities", 14 Nov 1993 (Box .09.13, Folder 99)
    - Laarman Sermons - "A Good Life", 2 Jan 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 100)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Epiphanies", 9 Jan 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 101)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Clinton in Memphis: Some Missing Pages", 16 Jan 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 102)
    - Laarman Sermons - "The Mind of Winter", 30 Jan 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 103)
    - Laarman Sermons - "The Communion of Saints", 6 Feb 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 104)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Isn't it Romantic?", 13 Feb 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 105)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Community as Practice (I)", 27 Feb 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 106)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Community as Practice (II)", 6 Mar 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 107)
    - Laarman Sermons - "One Covenant", 20 Mar 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 108)
    - Laarman Sermons - "While the City Waits", 27 Mar 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 109)
    - Laarman Sermons - "An Easter Celebration", 3 Apr 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 110)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Village People", 10 Apr 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 111)
    - Laarman Sermons - "A Sentimental Education", 24 Apr 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 112)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Workers of the World, Unite", 1 May 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 113)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Supermoms", 8 May 1998 (Box .09.13, Folder 114)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Virtual Reality", 15 May 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 115)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Tongues of Fire", 22 Apr 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 116)
    - Laarman Sermons - "E Pluribus Unum", 5 Jun 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 117)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Sexual Personae", 26 Jun 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 118)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Republican Virtue", 3 Jul 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 119)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Billary and Us: A Threnody", 31 Jul 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 120)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Godly Disillusionment", 7 Aug 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 121)
    - Laarman Sermons - "The Far Side of 50", 21 Aug 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 122)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Going for Broke", 28 Aug 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 123)
    - Laarman Sermons - "In Praise of Idleness", 4 Sep 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 124)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Commanded to Rest", 11 Sep 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 125)
    - Laarman Sermons - "The Unhealed Church", 18 Sep 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 126)
    - Laarman Sermons - "The Healing Church", 25 Sep 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 127)
    - Laarman Sermons - "A Bloodless Thanksgiving?", 2 Oct 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 128)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Sparing the Rod and Saving the Child", 9 Oct 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 129)
    - Laarman Sermons - "No Place for Grace", 30 Oct 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 130)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Ambiguous Affluence", 13 Nov 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 131)
    - Laarman Sermons - "The 'New Israel': Puritan Presumption & American Price", 20 Nov 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 132)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Teen Moms & Blessed Virgins", 27 Nov 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 133)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Penitential Purple", 4 Dec 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 134)
    - Laarman Sermons - "El Norte in Imagination & in Fact", 11 Dec 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 135)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Lo, How a Rose...", 18 Dec 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 136)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Meditation on the Magi", 25 Dec 1994 (Box .09.13, Folder 137)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Voice and Vocation in Dispiriting Times", 8 Jan 1995 (Box .09.13, Folder 138)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Recalling our Roots", 19 Jan 1995 (Box .09.13, Folder 139)
    - Laarman Sermons - "The Culture of Flattery", 22 Jan 1995 (Box .09.13, Folder 140)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Everyday People", 5 Feb 1995 (Box .09.13, Folder 141)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Be Mine", 12 Feb 1995 (Box .09.13, Folder 142)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Signs of the Time", 5 Mar 1995 (Box .09.13, Folder 143)
    - Laarman Sermons - "What's Art Got to Do With It?", 12 Mar 1995 (Box .09.13, Folder 144)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Anthem for Doomed Youth", 19 Mar 1995 (Box .09.13, Folder 145)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Prozac Nation", 2 Apr 1995 (Box .09.13, Folder 146)
    - Laarman Sermons - Maundy Thursday Service, 13 Apr 1995 (Box .09.14, Folder 1)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Meditation: The Seventh 'Word' from the Cross'", 14 Apr 1995 (Box .09.14, Folder 2)
    - Laarman Sermons - "And We are Witnesses", 16 Apr 1995 (Box .09.14, Folder 3)
    - Laarman Sermons - "God's Dysfunctional Families", 14 May 1995 (Box .09.14, Folder 4)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Two Meditations: 'On Wings of Song'", 21 May 1995 (Box .09.14, Folder 5)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Baptist and Blue", 11 Jun 1995 (Box .09.14, Folder 6)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Passing on the Legacy of Activism", 25 Jun 1995 (Box .09.14, Folder 7)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Language Theft & the Rhetoric of Reaction", 2 Jul 1995 (Box .09.14, Folder 8)
    - Laarman Sermons - "No Answer", 30 Jul 1995 (Box .09.14, Folder 9)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Credences of Summer", 30 Jul 1995 (Box .09.14, Folder 10)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Siren Songs", 10 Sep 1995 (Box .09.14, Folder 11)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Parables of Living", 24 Sep 1995 (Box .09.14, Folder 12)
    - Laarman Sermons - "The Doxological Imperative", 1 Oct 1995 (Box .09.14, Folder 13)
    - Laarman Sermons - Meditations, 22 Oct 1995 (Box .09.14, Folder 14)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Emotional Intelligence", 5 Nov 1995 (Box .09.14, Folder 15)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Remembering Satan", 26 Nov 1995 (Box .09.14, Folder 16)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Past Perfect: Future Indicative", 17 Dec 1995 (Box .09.14, Folder 17)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Night Vision", 24 Dec 1995 (Box .09.14, Folder 18)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Church as Adversary Culture", 7 Jan 1996 (Box .09.14, Folder 19)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Regulating the Poor", 21 Jan 1996 (Box .09.14, Folder 20)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Give Me the Simple Life", 28 Jan 1996 (Box .09.14, Folder 21)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Piety as Contested Terrain", 4 Feb 1996 (Box .09.14, Folder 22)
    - Laarman Sermons - "The Search for a Master Narrative, Part I: Of Mountains & Molehills", 18 Feb 1996 (Box .09.14, Folder 23)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Unauthorized Ministries: The Case for 'Sour Competency' in an Authoritarian Age", 3 Mar 1996 (Box .09.14, Folder 25)
    - Laarman Sermons - "New Horizons in the Healer's Art", 17 Mar 1996 (Box .09.14, Folder 26)
    - Laarman Sermons - "The Folly of Preaching", 24 Mar 1996 (Box .09.14, Folder 27)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Flawed Heroes & Flawed Followers", 31 Mar 1996 (Box .09.14, Folder 28)
    - Laarman Sermons - "The Hunger for More Light", 7 Apr 1996 (Box .09.14, Folder 29)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Sibling Rivalries", 14 Apr 1996 (Box .09.14, Folder 30)
    - Laarman Sermons - "The Earth is the Lord's", 28 Apr 1996 (Box .09.14, Folder 31)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Bad Mothers: Policing Maternal Ethics", 12 May 1996 (Box .09.14, Folder 32)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Mystical Communion in Song", 19 May 1996 (Box .09.14, Folder 33)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Would That All God's People Were Prophets?", 26 May 1996 (Box .09.14, Folder 34)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Life Together or Life Apart?", 2 Jun 1996 (Box .09.14, Folder 35)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Losing the Meaning of Politics in the 'Politics of meaning'", 23 Jun 1996 (Box .09.14, Folder 36)
    - Laarman Sermons - "To Have & To Hold: The Gay Marriage Controversy", 30 Jun 1996 (Box .09.14, Folder 37)
    - Laarman Sermons - "People Are Still Having Sex?", 14 Jul 1996 (Box .09.14, Folder 38)
    - Laarman Sermons - "When We Were Good", 11 Aug 1996 (Box .09.14, Folder 39)
    - Laarman Sermons - "The Age of Self-Importance", 25 Aug 1996 (Box .09.14, Folder 40)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Hard Currency: Falling Wages", 1 Sep 1996 (Box .09.14, Folder 41)
    - Laarman Sermons - "After Virtue", 8 Sep 1996 (Box .09.14, Folder 42)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Millenial Realism", 22 Sep 1996 (Box .09.14, Folder 43)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Tooth Fairy Stewardship", 29 Sep 1996 (Box .09.14, Folder 44)
    - Laarman Sermons - "On Choosing the Lesser of Two Evils", 20 Oct 1996 (Box .09.14, Folder 45)
    - Laarman Sermons - "An Avalanche of Crud", 3 Nov 1996 (Box .09.14, Folder 46)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Keeping Home Fires Burning", 17 Nov 1996 (Box .09.14, Folder 47)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Elegy with Variations" World AIDS Day, 1 Dec 1996 (Box .09.14, Folder 48)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Words Within the Words", 15 Dec 1996 (Box .09.14, Folder 49)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Augenblick", 19 Dec 1996 (Box .09.14, Folder 50)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Speaking of God After Long Silence", 5 Jan 1997 (Box .09.14, Folder 51)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Liberal Orthodoxy: Gone But Not Forgotten", 26 Jan 1997 (Box .09.14, Folder 52)
    - Laarman Sermons - "In the Wilderness", 16 Feb 1997 (Box .09.14, Folder 54)
    - Laarman Sermons - "Giving Sin a Bad Name", 9 Mar 1997 (Box .09.14, Folder 55)